Just a little find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find find
I'm in love with a character who's smart and intelligent.
I've been thinking about changing lately, but I don't know what it is.
Samjen, I don't even have a car.
That's the café that Yuka likes...
I want to change recently...
I'm going to go to Costco and buy a bunch of stuff...
So I went to Costco and bought a bunch of stuff!
I don't mean "shopping" anymore, I mean "buying"!
Ta-da!
I bought bagels!
Hello everyone!
This is Ayumi Ozawa of Nearly Call Joy
Mizuki Hashimoto
Yuka Murayama.
Yay!
Yes, already, as you all noticed, it's windy.
Look, it's windy.
Where do you think they are?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Oh, you heard that.
No, I'm not.
This time, we're in Chiba.
Yay!
This time, we are going on a near-joyful shopping trip for girls.
This time, we are going to do nothing but shopping!
Yay!
I'm so happy, there's nothing more to say!
But you know what? When we were talking...
I was told to just shop today.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't that great?
He asked me to do some shopping.
Juice.
Hey, hey.
I know why you're smiling.I know why you're smiling.
It's your hair, isn't it?
I know why you're smiling.
Why are you smiling? I know why.
So this time, we're really...
I'm going to show you our real life on our real day off.
I think you'll be able to see something that you can't see in our regular videos.
I think you'll be able to see something of us that you wouldn't normally see in a video project.
I hope you enjoy it!
Yay!
Now, now...
Let's get to the point right away.
We're here at the Aqualine Sea Hotel.
There seem to be a lot of stores inside.
So let's go and have a stroll.
Have fun!
Okay, I'm off!
Wait, first of all, look at the sea.
Our back
It's in the middle of Kanagawa and Chiba
So it feels like we're right in the middle of the ocean
I feel like we're in the middle of the ocean
You know, we're right in the middle of the ocean.
We've been through the ocean, you know
Under the sea
Come on in, Mitsuki!
You were talking so much just now.
Oh!
The cameras are rolling.
Oh, no.
We're, you know, goofing around a lot.
Yeah, we do.
So we're just gonna goof around a little bit today.
Oh, thank you.
I'm gonna be a goofball.I think I'm going to be.
Hey.
The ocean is so beautiful.
Oh, hey.
What do you think? Hey, Mitsuki?
Mitsuki?
Uh...
A little tighter.
Here, here.
Mitsuki?
Oh, Aimi did this.
It looks good.
Let's have fun.
What do you want to do?
Something on your mind?
You know, it's like there's no food, right?
Maybe. Is there?
Rice is a souvenir?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It looks delicious.
You're buying? I bought it. I ate it.
Where is it?
I'm sure it's delicious.
Why don't we just eat this?
Seafood skewers!
Nice octopus skewers!
That looks good.
Where is it? Here.
Just now.
Oh, this way.
Yeah, this way.
Oh, there it is.
I didn't see it.
There it is.There it is.
Oh, it looks delicious!
Wow, it looks like a mansei!
I want some takotate!
Squid.
I want some!
Wow! Thank you so much!
So, I got it.
We got it.
What happened?
What did you get?
So, we got it.
You're a funny host now, aren't you?
I'm glad to host.
Yuka got the sardines. Sardines?
Sardines?
What about you?
Scallops.
Scallops are big, aren't they?
So big.
I'll have the iidako.
Looks delicious.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
It smells like seafood.
Is it good?
It's good.
Is this... is this chopsticks?
Chopsticks?
Are they honey?
I think they're chopsticks.
Chopsticks.Chopsticks and all.
Maybe, you know, they didn't think I'd eat alone.
Like share-happy with everyone.
soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
This is sardine fried with black salt!
Looks delicious, like some kind of candy!
Hoku-hoku?
I heard it's delicious!
Jaime is a translator too!
Translator?
Translator!
It's so stuffed.
And flaky.
Yeah.
Very crispy.
Yuka says it's very tasty.
Looks delicious.
Is that right?
Correct?
Gentle.
Correct.
Bon appétit.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Delicious
Yum.
What do you think?
The scallops are nice.
Oh, yes. Yes, it is.
It's good.
Thank you.
It's so comforting.
But first... we're moving on. Look at the beautiful sea we're eating...
What's with you?
Boo-boo, wow, it's beautiful. There's nothing but the sea.
And oh, is it coming?And I wonder if he'll come.
And then I'll call you and you'll say you'll send me. a I won't throw it, turn around and look at me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Whale bark bark bark bark bark.
He wants to see.
I want to see.
Boo-boo... now... you've been watching the sea... please explain what happened... three things happened...
I'm going to something, but the octopus was too energetic and ran away.
I've been thinking that I'd like to go to the beach with that smart, nice bag of yours...
Why is it so important to say "boo-boo" when you've just turned 20 years old?
I'd like to change my character to a smart character, a clever character, a smart guy, a brainy guy.
I've been thinking about changing my character, but I don't know how I've been so far... but I've always been smart, but not that smart.
I've been hiding it, but I've been watching him mutate, and he's really weird.
I wonder what I'm going to say to him...
I love you and I love our Taiwan, you're so important to us!
I don't know what to say, but it's nice.
I'm just saying...
I've got a nice and funny toddler here.
Una
greens
Cut it out.
I'm a fosterer.
I'm just trying to be nice.
I'll be fine, please.
And my wife... Ну, I'm sure she'll be fine.
And the last of the breeders.
Well, I'm a power eater. I want a head, a tail, or a big belly.
I'm not talking about "Enter", I'm talking about "Shabon". I wonder which one is the tire key.
I'm not talking about "Enter", I'm talking about "Shaboom".
It's decided, it's decided, today's the day!
Today's the day!
Yeah, the head, of course... but the takoyaki is the tail...
I'd rather eat from the head first, it's more mature.
It's like this will make you smarter... that's what I'll do.
It's true that both tayaki and tayaki are packed with ideas when you eat them head first.Well, they're both from the head.
The tail is a little less doughy than the head, so it's more refreshing.
It's a warm and mature way to eat.
Thank you very much.
It's so cute!
It's so cute, all arms full!
Who's that?
Nia Joy.
Okay, this is Nia Joy's.
Horizontal Leavey, whose?
The Horizontal Levee.
This is Near Joy's sanctum sanctorum.
I'll say it myself.
And that brings us to the outlet store... Mitsui Outlet Park.
We're here at the park. Kisarazu.
Look at these big letters! I've never been here before!
I've never been to an outlet store before.
Do you have a 10% discount?
It's an outlet park.
I've never seen a b&b store in here.
Concealer, right?
Concealer? Is it good?
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the sponcealer.
Oh, it's Yuka's favorite café.
Hey, hey, hey!
Denjan.
What's it called?
Denderka.
Dendian
DD's
Everybody loves
Everybody Loves Cafe
Oh, great.
Gelapickey's Cafe.
Let's go to the crepe, let's get some Yay crepes.Let's go. I'm going to the crepe place. Let's get an "Yay Crepe".
I'm going, too. What did you order?
I got the butter and sugar crepe, the simple crepe with pistachio ice cream topping.
Yay! What about you, Yuka?
I ordered a crepe with pistachio cream and pistachio ice cream topping.
Everyone else, pistachio ice cream. Yuka?
I'm with Misaki Ozawa. It's short for "science.
Let's eat. Thank you for the food.
I'm so happy. I've been curious about this place.
Delicious.
So rich.
It's great.
Very rich.
You have a nice expression.
I'll have some too.
It's very rich.
Isn't it rich?
Everyone likes pistachios, right?
I love pistachios.
You like pistachios?
Ayama likes pistachios.
They're kind of chunky, aren't they?
When you scoop them with a spoon
I get the pistachio nuts right.
Where did they come from?
What is it?
I just went through it myself.
But you two were so quiet.
I don't know, I just can't go through with it.
What is it? Penser's flavor?
Flavor? What? Nutty?
I know, I know.
How do you say nutty? Nutty?
What? But crab?
A mango is a crab.
It doesn't have the same texture.No texture, right?
It's good.
And it's good.
Ta-da! Beard.
What? What?
Drink, drink, drink.
I chewed it.
Hey, can you just cut that out already?
I'm pretty sure he's using it.
It's just... - Here we go.
Until then.
But you're better than I.M., aren't you?
If I have to go...
But you're good.
Oh, you're good.
Look at you!
Yo! Beard!
Let's pump!
You're so cute.
Yo!
Yo, yo, yo, yo...
Hiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyohiyo.
Let's have some.
Normal.
Bon appétit.
Let's eat.
Can we go to the plaza?
Yeah, plaza's fine.
And makeup.
Yeah, I really want a lipstick.
And some other stuff.
I went shopping.
I bought Hashihara-san's Lilimu lipstick.
It's a new color. Everyone bought a new color.
There were a lot of them. They just arrived at the store.
I'm so happy. We were able to get them. All of them.Glad I got it. I was able to get it. Hey, guys.
What number did you get? Yuka.
I bought the sheer No. 2.
Pink?
Yes. Pink fondue.
We are 1.
I got the Happy Red.
Enjoy.
Nice purchase. Matching.
Thank you.
What can I get for you?
You've had a lot of fun, haven't you?
I got to eat crepes.
I could eat.
I was able to shop.
Surprisingly, it's late in the evening.
It doesn't feel like it.
It's early.
I have Nico Hand.
Nico Hand?
I bought a purse.
I have this bag and Nico Hand.
It's nice.
It's really nice.
Is your birthday coming?
You have a birthday?
You said it was yesterday.
You predicted it.
You said Mizuki was going to say it.
Yes, I did.
We were talking about deciding on the ban.
I'll decide in this short time.
Decide?
The way to Costco.
I think you'll understand better now that it's on audio.I think the audio makes it more understandable.
Sure.
What would you like?
One for all?
I guess so.
Why don't you turn it around?
It's okay.
If we're on the move, we can use katakana NG, can't we?
No katakana?
Let's just speak in Japanese.
Okay.
Do as you wish.
I'll let you do the "no katakana" project on your own.
I did it on my own.
I tried it.
I'll ask them if they've tried anything.
Isn't it a bit like YouTube?
It sure does.
I picked it up at a donkey's shop, but it's close by.
I picked it up.
I took a walk.
Yes, one more time.
That's the plan.
I tried to get a half-price discount at the supermarket.
I tried to get it.
I tried to see how many convenience stores I could visit from the station to my house.
That's planning.
You have a good planning rate.
I never exceeded one.
I just listened to what they said.
I just let it be what I heard.
That's no longer working.
I've been listening.
I'm running out.
Oh, no.Oh no.
So, Mitsui Outlet Park, Kisarazu.
We did a lot of shopping, but how was it?
It was fun no matter what.
I was satisfied.
It was pretty fulfilling.
I also got a lot of stuff.
I'm happy. Really happy.
There are some places that don't sell them.
I had fun at my first outlet park.
We had crepes, and then this.
Almost jam.
Another 1,2,3,4,5,6. 6 jars.
Jars.
You were very satisfied and had a good shopping experience, weren't you?
Yes.
So, today is not over yet.
There is more shopping to do.
There is more.
The next one will be the last.
Guess where we are going next.
Take a guess.
Last but not least, everyone is getting pretty fired up, aren't they?
We're all really into it, aren't we?
It's a Miyagi shopping trip for girls, you know.
There's more to come.
Let's do lots of shopping!
Please enjoy the rest of the trip.
I'm going to move on.
I'm off.
Yes, so I went to Costco and bought a bunch of stuff.
Yay.
I'm already shopping, or rather, I'm buying a lot.
That's right.
I bought a lot.
Everyone has their own bag.Everyone has their own bag.
I bought so many bags that I had to buy more.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It was fun. How was it?
How did you like it?
I bought it just the way I wanted it.
Everyone was so enthusiastic about it.
Okay, I'm going to buy it.
It was sparkling.
I bought a lot.
Let me introduce you.
What do you say?
Shall we go to Yuka-san?
Let's go!
I bought bagels.
Yuka-san loves bagels.
Yes, she loves bagels so much, so much, so much.
There are days when I have bagels for three meals a day.
Yes, really.
You are a maniac.
Yes, I've been eating bagels for a long time.
Costco's bagels are the best.
Sounds good. What flavor?
I bought a blueberry flavor and a cinnamon raisin bagel flavor.
They are good.
And they were cheap.
Two for 800 yen.
That's good. I've already counted them.
Bagel bagel.
I'm going to start living on bagels from now on.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Have a wonderful bagel life.
It's true.It's true.
We bought matching items.
Matching.
What do you think it is?
I'm coming.
Go ahead.
Ready?
Ta-da!
Salmon.
Oh, no.
Such a big salmon.
Oh, man.
It's a big salmon, isn't it?
And you guys didn't intend to buy Ayumi, did you?
I like it, but salmon.
It's so big.
I was wondering what to do,
They were so excited that they said they would definitely buy it.
It's delicious.
Yes, Mitsuki especially likes salmon.
We both had salmon-like meat, right?
I grew up with it.
I was talking about it earlier.
From Costco?
My mom always says that,
I'm sure this is what she'll have after the new grand prize competition.
It's a memory.
Memorabilia.
I wasn't planning on buying it because I was drawn to the two,
I noticed it was in my basket.
But I'm happy because I love salmon.
I also bought some bread.
This is a bread.
It looks like Costco.
Yes, Costco is like dinner rolls, isn't it?
It's like Costco is a dinner roll, isn't it?I feel like I'm a good person, don't you?
I'm glad.
I am this.
This is it.
This is the vanilla flavor of Oikosu yogurt.
There are many times when they don't have vanilla flavor, right?
I know, I go to Costco and they don't have it at least that often.
And even if I go there, it's often like they don't have it,
I didn't think they had vanilla flavor today, and I thought I wouldn't buy this, so I did.
I like protein, so I had to buy this.
I also bought the chicken meat.
I'm glad.
So much.
I bought more than I can introduce.
We had a blast.
It was fun.
It was really fun.
I hope you all enjoyed seeing how many of us there are.
I hope you all enjoyed seeing how we are usually like.
There might have been some goofy scenes that we don't usually show.
I forgot the sound, so I may have laughed a lot at some parts where I wondered what the point was.
Is it okay if I don't talk?
I'm fine.
Is it okay?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Who do you want to recommend?
No, I don't.
There's salmon.
All of them?
So, if you liked this video and are happy to see everyone's recommendations,
If you enjoyed this video, please click the "Good" button, leave a comment, or subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
This is Miyalee Colejoy.
Bye bye.Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye. Thank you very much.
So, I did a lot of shopping, but I also bought something for the members.
Then, you don't have any, do you, Amitsuki?
This way, sir.
It's Jagabee's Sushi Taste.
Yes, I bought Jagabee's sushi flavor.
I'm so glad I did, because I was wondering what to buy for everyone.
It's so hard to decide.
Last time Anna and Mayuka bought Jagarico, right?
So I thought...
But this time I decided to buy a jagabee.
Great. I'm going to go for the jagarico.
Wait for me.
Thank you.